My lord, you’re here.
What are you doing here?
Someone disrespected Lord Redmond.
I came to handle it,
but they’re stronger than expected.
We need your
elite forces, my lord.
-Who?
That bench over there, and those two miners!
Lady Cassia.
He belongs to you?
Did he offend you, my lady?
Offending me is minor.
But he threatened
to kill Lord Severin.
That is a very big problem.
What?!
I’m here.
Lord Severin, forgive me!
This is my failure
to control my subordinates.
I’ll deal with him immediately.
My lord, what are you doing?
He's just a disowned bastard. Don't fall for his act!
Shut your mouth.
My lord, no!
Please!
It’s handled, my lord.
Please forgive me.
You know the punishment
for offending Lord Severin.
I know.
I’ll sever my own
right arm right here!
You came for my wedding today?
Y-yes, my lord.
Since you came to congratulate
me,
I’ll spare you this once.
Thank you, my lord!
Bring the gifts!
From Black Raven City: A
legendary Dragon Egg worth ten million!
Three ancient magic codexes!
A Golden Dragon stallion!
And twenty million raw gold coins!
Take it back.
The Scott family canceled the wedding.
What?
Canceled?
The noble Lady Livia
declared that a lowly
miner like me
is unworthy of her.
She is marrying Redmond instead.
She wants to marry who?
Who is Redmond?
Lord Darren, Severin is
just a disowned bastard.
Why do you
respect him so much?
You’re telling me Lord Severin
is a disowned son of yours?